Lots of times we can feel triggered and want to stay away or get angry, but other times
we might feel numb.
Numb means you don't feel any emotions about something.
It happens when you have seen, felt, or heard something bad so many times that you don't
react anymore.
This numb feeling can happen with good things too.
It's when someone doesn't look forward to or enjoy happy events anymore.
They just feel bleh.
Sometimes at a happy event like a birthday party they might even feel angry or sad.
So kids can be triggered by good or bad things.
Sometimes they feel numb and other times they get really upset.
We all have triggers.
These are things that affect us a lot.
They can change how we think.
For example, because his gym teacher is mean, Mike might start thinking people can't be
trusted, or he might think the world is scary, or that there is something wrong with him,
even when there isn't.
These thoughts can change how we feel.
Someone who is often triggered might feel afraid, angry, sad, bored, or upset most of
the day.